const jsfunQuestions = [
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "Which keyword would you use to declare a variable that you will not change?",
    answers: [
      "`var`",
      "`let`",
      "`const`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`const`"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "If you don't want a variable to be block scoped, which keyword would you use?",
    answers: [
      "`let`",
      "`var`",
      "`const`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`var`"
  },
  {
    category: "ES6",
    question: "True or False: `var` names are hoisted with their values.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "ES6",
    question: "True or False: function names are hoisted with their contents.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "true"
  },
  {
    category: "context",
    question: "What is the default reference for `this`?",
    answers: [
      "the global window object",
      "the DOM",
      "an arrow function"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "the global window object"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What does the callback in a `.forEach()` return?",
    answers: [
      "a truthy value",
      "the accumulator",
      "`undefined`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`undefined`"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What does `.map()` return?",
    answers: [
      "the current element",
      "a modified array of the same length",
      "an array of a different length",
      "a truthy value"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "a modified array of the same length"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What does the `.filter()` callback return?",
    answers: [
      "an array of a different length",
      "the current element",
      "true or false",
      "an array of a different length"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "true or false"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "True or False: accessor methods will change the original array.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What method would you use if you want a copy of an object so you can mutate it?",
    answers: [
      "`.map()`",
      "`.reduce()`",
      "`object.assign()`",
      "`object.keys()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`object.assign()`"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "Which method takes in two parameters?",
    answers: [
      "`.find()`",
      "`.reduce()`",
      "`.map()`",
      "`object.keys()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`.reduce()`"
  },
  {
    category: "context",
    question: "True or False: when using the `new` keyword, `this` refers to the prototype object.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "context",
    question: "True or False: the value of `this` is set when an arrow function is created in memory.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "Is javascript synchronous or asynchronous?",
    answers: [
      "synchronous",
      "asynchronous"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "synchronous"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "True or False: `let` and `const` are not hoisted.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "True or False: scope and context are virtually the same.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "True or False: function execution context and scope are virtually the same.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "true"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "The value of `this` is assigned during which phase of interpretation?",
    answers: [
      "execution phase",
      "creation phase"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "creation phase"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "Which method would you use if you wanted just an array of the keys of an object?",
    answers: [
      "`.filter()`",
      "`object.keys()`",
      "`.reduce()`",
      "`.map()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`object.keys()`"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What is the first parameter you must pass in to `object.assign()`?",
    answers: [
      "callback",
      "current element",
      "target object",
      "source object"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "target object"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What should you use to merge multiple objects into a single object?",
    answers: [
      "`.reduce()`",
      "`.filter()`",
      "spread operator",
      "`object.assign()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`object.assign()`"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "Which of these is not an accessor method (it mutates the original array)?",
    answers: [
      "`.sort()`",
      "`.join()`",
      "`.slice()`",
      "`.push()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`.sort()`"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What type of method is `.reduce()`?",
    answers: [
      "accessor method",
      "iteration method",
      "mutator method"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "iteration method"
  },
  {
    category: "prototype methods",
    question: "What method could you use to get an array of an object's key value pairs?",
    answers: [
      "`object.keys()`",
      "`object.assign()`",
      "`object.entries()`",
      "`.forEach()`"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "`object.entries()`"
  },
  {
    category: "context",
    question: "Where can we change the value of `this`?",
    answers: [
      "we can't",
      "inside a function",
      "with `object.this()`",
      "using a variable declaration"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "inside a function"
  },
  {
    category: "context",
    question: "In a named ES5 function, the value of `this` is set when:",
    answers: [
      "the function is created",
      "the function is invoked",
      "the function has returned something"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "the function is invoked"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "When are the variable declarations assigned values?",
    answers: [
      "execution phase",
      "creation phase",
      "hoisting"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "execution phase"
  },
  {
    category: "ES6",
    question: "True or False: arrow functions can always replace regular functions.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "false"
  },
  {
    category: "ES6",
    question: "When would you want to use a regular function instead of an arrow function?",
    answers: [
      "click handlers",
      "object methods",
      "prototype methods",
      "all of the above"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "all of the above"
  },
  {
    category: "scope",
    question: "True or False: from outside of a function, we can't access that function's local variables unless they are returned from it.",
    answers: [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    correctAnswer: "true"
  }
]


module.exports = { jsfunQuestions };